Now we're going to look at persistent footer buttons. It's another hidden gem here. It's actually along the bottom. This area right here is called the footer.
And in there you can put just about anything you want. So let's go ahead and fill this in. First thing, we want a variable.
And let's make a function. Let's change that to lowercase just to be consistent.
Alright, now we can get down to business here.
You can see persistent footer buttons takes an array of widgets. Widgets, meaning we can use any control we want.
In here, let's just say new icon button. And let's just randomly grab some. And let's just make a few of these.
Set these to just random icons so we can tell they're different.
And hot reload has picked up. As you can see, here's our footer area.
And here's our buttons. Let's go ahead and change this so we can see that update when we click.
And you can see the value changes.
Simple and easy way to put controls at the bottom of the screen.
Right all from the screen.